Gerard Designs Collection of Mold Drawings
Gerard Designs Collection of Mold Drawings
- Drawings
  - #1846: 2 cavity mold handle and latch, 1976; made for Family Products (Box 14)
  - #1848: 16 cavity mold rubber liner, 1976; made for Lastomerex Inc. (Box 14)
  - #1850: 4 cavity mold stove parts, 1976; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 14)
  - #1858: 2 cavity mold diaphragm 80 oz decantor, 1976; made for Family Products (Box 14)
  - #1862: 4 cavity tray mold, 1976; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 14)
  - #1867: 64 cavity mold 402000 bushing, 1976; made for Lastomerex Inc. (Box 14)
  - #1872: 2 cavity mold quick disconnect, 1976; made for Nalge Co. (Box 14)
  - #1877: 8 cavity mold 15/125 test tube, 1976; made for Wachusett Molding (Box 14)
  - #1881: 2 cavity (room for 4) yoke ring handle, 1976; made for Phillips MFG (Box 14)
  - #1883: 8 cavity mold light shield, 1976; made for Phillips MFG (Box 14)
  - #1885: 4 cavity mold rivet gun trigger, 1976; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 14)
  - #1889: 8 cavity mold compact bezel, 1976; made for L&L Tool Co. (Box 14)
  - #1910: 2 cavity mold 1.5 litre jar, 1976; made for Family Products (Box 14)
  - #1911: 1 cavity mold 8" cover, 1976; made for Family Products (Box 15)
  - #1912: 1 cavity mold 8" diaphragm, 1976; made for Family Products (Box 15)
  - #1913: 1 cavity plunger mold, 1976; made for Family Products (Box 15)
  - #1920-1922: 1 cavity oral frame mold, 1976; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 15)
  - #1923: 8 cavity mold 2238-68 housing, 1976; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 15)
  - #1924: 8 cavity mold 2238-69 base, 1976; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 15)
  - #1926: 4 cavity 12x75 tube mold, 1976; made for Wachusett Molding Corp. (Box 15)
  - #1927: 4 cavity mold access slide, 1976; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 15)
  - #1928: 2 cavity mold top housing, 1976; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 15)
  - #1929: 2 cavity mold hottom housing, 1976; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 15)
  - #1930: 2 cavity mold 15ml conical centrifuge tube, 1976; made for Nalge (Box 15)
  - #1932: 1 cavity mold telephone base index cover, 1976; made for Nylon Products Inc. (Box 15)
  - #1933: 1 cavity mold telephone base index tray, 1976; made for Nylon Products Inc. (Box 15)
  - #1934: 1 cavity mold transducer dome, 1976; made for Hewlett Packard (Box 15)
  - #1935: 8 cavity mold strap clip, 1976; made for Girouoard Tool & Die, Inc. (Box 15)
  - #1936: 4 cavity mold item 1710 can-do parts, 1976; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 15)
  - #1937: 2 cavity grill mold, 1976; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 15)
  - #1939: 2 cavity mold transducer housing and cover, 1976; made for Hewlett Packard (Box 15)
  - #1941: 1 cavity mold 12" flower pot, 1976; made for Lockwood Plastics (Box 15)
  - #1942: 1 cavity saucer mold, 1976; made for Lockwood Plastics (Box 16)
  - #1944: 2 cavity mold dormer roof, 1976; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 16)
  - #1948: 2 cavity mold top, 1976; made for General Electric (Box 16)
  - #1949: 2 cavity mold resevoir, 1976; made for General Electric (Box 16)
  - #1950: 2 cavity mold base, 1976; made for General Electric (Box 16)
  - #1951: 2 cavity mold base plate, 1976; made for General Electric (Box 16)
  - #1952: 2 cavity mold basket, 1976; made for General Electric (Box 16)
  - #1953: 2 cavity mold handle, 1976; made for General Electric (Box 16)
  - #1954: 2 cavity mold carafe lid, 1976; made for General Electric (Box 16)
  - #1955: 2 cavity mold spreader cover, 1976; made for General Electric (Box 16)
  - #1957: 2 cavity mold cabinet front, 1976; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 16)
  - #1963: 1 cavity mold combat top housing, 1976; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 16)
  - #1964: single cavity mold bottom housing, 1976; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 16)
  - #1968: 4 cavity mold combat battery door, 1976; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 16)
  - #1970: cocktail shaker cover, 1976; made for Bay State Plastics (Box 16)
  - #1973: 4 cavity mold cable caps, 1977; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 16)
  - #1976: 3 cavity (room for 6) housing, base, and door, 1977; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 16)
  - #1980: 3 cavity mold module housing, 1977; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 17)
  - #1984: 12 cavity mold arian compact base, 1977; made for L&L Tool Co. (Box 17)
  - #1990: 1 cavity mold arcade housing top, 1977; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 17)
  - #1991: single cavity mold arcade bottom housing, 1977; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 17)
  - #2007: 18 cavity mold, 16 cav. sub, 2 cav. rule, Pakrer project #679, 1977; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 17)
  - #2010: 4 cavity mold rail mounting plate, 1977; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 17)
  - #2011: 2 cavity mold score wheel, 1977; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 17)
  - #2012: 96 cavity mold riveton rivet, 1977; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 17)
  - #2014: coat hanger 18" plain, 1977; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 17)
  - #2016: 2 cavity mold right and left wheel, 1977; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 17)
  - #2020: 2 cavity mold transmitter cap and housing, 1977; made for Girouoard Tool & Die, Inc. (Box 17)
  - #2022: 1 cavity mold mirror and case parts, 1977; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 17)
  - #2027: 4 cavity mold travel hanger, 1977; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 17)
  - #2032: 1 cavity (room for 2) director 3 end cap, 1977; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 17)
  - #2035: 4 cavity mold extension, 1977; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 17)
  - #2037: 4 cavity mold timer knob, 1977; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 17)
  - #2042: 8 cavity mold insert handle grid, 1977; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 17)
  - #2045: 4 cavity mold shooter, 1977; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 17)
  - #2048: 4 cavity mold board brace connector, 1977; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 17)
  - #2051: 4 cavity mold spool, 1977; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 18)
  - #2052: single cavity mold end bell (face comm.), 1977; made for McCord (Box 18)
  - #2054: 4 cavity mold combined stem and collar, 1977; made for Nypro (Box 18)
  - #2055: 6 cavity mold table leg, 1977; made for Gotham Industries Inc. (Box 18)
  - #2056: 8 cavity mold linear pot knob, 1977; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 18)
  - #2057: 2-4 cavity mold units #57669 switch cap, 1977; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 18)
  - #2058: 4 cavity mold flipper button insert, 1977; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 18)
  - #2059: 2 cavity mold ball ejector-insert, 1977; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 18)
  - #2062: 4 cavity mold bumper guard, 1977; made for Coleco Industries Inc. (Box 18)
  - #2074: single cavity mold sizzle tray, 1977; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 18)
  - #2076: 4 cavity mold aqua sweep collar, 1977; made for Nypro (Box 18)
  - #2079: 2 cavity mold cover, 1977; made fo rGeneral Electric (Box 18)
  - #2080: 2 cavity mold filter insert, 1977; made for General Electric (Box 18)
  - #2092: 2 cavity mold front panel, 1977; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 18)
  - #2107: single cavity mold cake dish, 1977; made for Girouoard Tool & Die, Inc. (Box 18)
  - #2108: single cavity mold cover, 1977; made for Girouoard Tool & Die, Inc. (Box 18)
  - #2112: 2 cavity mold 4" saucer, 1977; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 18)
  - #2113: 2 cavity mold 5.5" saucer, 1977; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 18)
  - #2115: 8 cavity mold stunt cycle wheel, 1977; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 18)
  - #2119: base inserts 4" and 5 1/2" flower pots, 1977; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 18)
  - #2121: 16 cavity mold check valve adaptor, 1977 (Box 18)
  - #2123: 2 cavity mold simon base and cover, 1977; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 18)
  - #2124: 4 cavity mold simon lens, 1977; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 19)
  - #2131: 2 cavity foam mold remote housing keyboard, 1977; made for County Tool & Die Co. (Box 19)
  - #2136: 6 cavity mold seat, popper and cam, 1977; made for Playskool Inc. (Box 19)
  - #2140: 3 cavity mold frame and bracket, 1977; made for Paragon Plastics (Box 19)
  - #2142: 12 cavity mold drop wire ring, 1977; made for Synthetic Products MFG Co. (Box 19)
  - #2143: 2 cavity mold P-15112 base, 1978; made for Synthetic Products MFG Co. (Box 19)
  - #2148: 4 cavity mold shower head parts, 1977; made for Pryde Inc. (Box 19)
  - #2149: 12 oz tumbler, undated; made for Vertex Tool & Die Co. (Box 19)
  - #2151: 8 cavity family mold triple play parts, 1977; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 19)
  - #2152: 2 cavity mold turntable and apron, 1977; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 19)
  - #2157: 4 cavity mold baffle and wheel housing, 1978; made for Playskool Inc. (Box 19)
  - #2160: 4 cavity mold (2 cav each) latch and washer, 1978; made for Byden Plastics Co. (Box 19)
  - #2174: 10 cavity mold starbird parts, 1978; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 19)
  - #2184: single cavity mold for 25lb fish container, 1978; made for Helubel (Box 19)
  - #2185: 10 cavity mold (2) reaction strip (8) serum cup, 1978; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 19)
  - #2200: 4 cavity mold General Electric knob, 1978; made for Turn Key Plastics Corp. (Box 19)
  - #2201: 4 cavity mold General Electric smart button, 1978; made for Turn Key Plastics Corp. (Box 19)
  - #2202: 4 cavity mold General Electric slide knob, 1978; made for Turn Key Plastics Corp. (Box 19)
  - #2204: 1 cavity mold battery section, 1978; 2 folders; made for Hardigg Industries Inc. (Box 20)
  - #2211: 24 cavity mold horseshoe, 1978; made for Turn Key Plastics Corp. (Box 20)
  - #2213: 1 cavity mold chloe cover, 1978; made for Creative Packaging (Box 20)
  - #2215: single cavity injection mold top cover, 1978; made for Bur-Bak Machine Corp. (Box 20)
  - #2221: 2 cavity mold locking strip (bent pin), 1978; made for Synthetic Products (Box 20)
  - #2224: 1 cavity mold for 16" salad bowl, 1978; made for E.B. Kingman Co. (Box 20)
  - #2227: 2 cavity mold sump cover, 1978; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 20)
  - #2228: 1 cavity mold center plate, 1978; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 20)
  - #2235: 4 cavity mold spool, 1978; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 20)
  - #2236: 4 cavity mold disc release lever, 1978; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 20)
  - #2240: 2 cavity mold pile on tray, 1978; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 21)
  - #2251: 2 cavity mold base and top signal jumper, 1978; made for Bur-Bak Machine Corp. (Box 21)
  - #2256: 6 cavity mold intruder parts, 1978; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 21)
  - #2257: 16 cavity mold intruder parts, 1978; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 21)
  - #2269: 4 cavity mold display lens, 1978; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 21)
  - #2270: 4 cavity mold powder box cover, 1978; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 21)
  - #2276: 14 cavity mold big cat parts, 1979; 2 folders; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 21)
  - #2277: 5 cavity mold dumper parts, 1978; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 21)
  - #2279: 4 cavity mold project #10 lens, 1978; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 21)
  - #2281: 4 cavity mold soap tray, 1978; made for J&R Mold Co. (Box 21)
  - #2284: 6 cavity mold misc. lens spacers, 1979; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 21)
  - #2285: 2 cavity mold filter bracket and holder, 1979; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 22)
  - #2286: 4 cavity mold screw and dial, 1979; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 22)
  - #2290: 4 cavity mold project #10 battery cover, 1979; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 22)
  - #2292: 12 cavity mold LCD cartridge parts, 1979; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 22)
  - #2298: 16 cavity mold stak pak, 1979; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 22)
  - #2302: 12 cavity mold gribbit parts, 1979; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 22)
  - #2303: 2 gravity mold gribbit base, 1979; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 22)
  - #2304: single cavity mold 17" roof, 1979; made for Bur-Bak Machine Corp. (Box 22)
  - #2305: 4 cavity mold electrode holder, 1979; made for Orion Research Inc. (Box 22)
  - #2320: 6 cavity mold protector housing, 1979; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 22)
  - #2324: 1 cavity mold milk claw bottom part, 1979; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 22)
  - #2329: 4 cavity mold rom leg connector, 1979; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 22)
  - #2330: 2 cavity mold 6" salad bowl, 1979; made for E.B. Kingman Co. (Box 22)
  - #2332: 2 cavity drive shaft hold, 1979; made for Altus Corp. (Box 22)
  - #2333, undated (Box 23)
  - #2336: 2 cavity mold strainer and vial, 1979 (Box 23)
  - #2338: 2 cavity mold super simon top insert, 1979; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 23)
  - #2339: 2 cavity mold instrument panel, 1979; made for KLH (Box 23)
  - #2343: 1 cavity mold front panel and MRA console, 1979; made for Aritech Corp. (Box 23)
  - #2344: 48 cavity mold can't stop mover, 1979; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 23)
  - #2350: 4 cavity mold tongue depressor, 1979; made for Medical Polymers Inc. (Box 23)
  - #2356: 14 cavity mold bottle type mascara wiper, 1979; made for L&L Mold Co. (Box 23)
  - #2359: 6 cavity mold 1 quart flower pot, 1979; made for Olde Leyden Corp. (Box 23)
  - #2364: 4 cavity mold 1 quart pot saucer, 1979; made for Olde Leyden Corp. (Box 23)
  - #2369: 1 cavity mold radio front, 1979 (Box 23)
  - #2372: 1 cavity mold 7 12" flower pot, 1979; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 23)
  - #2374: 2 cavity mold 5" flower pot, 1979; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 23)
  - #2376: 44 cavity mold key button, 1979; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 23)
  - #2382: 1 cavity mold calander strand, 1979; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 23)
  - #2383: 40 cavity mold strap (handle), 1979; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 23)
  - #2385: 1 cavity mold keyboard base, 1979; made for ICL Inc. (Box 23)
  - #2386: 1 cavity mold keyboard insert, 1979; made for ICL Inc. (Box 24)
  - #2387: 4 cavity (room for 8) mold push button, 1979; made for KLH Randd Corp. (Box 24)
  - #2388: 2 cavity mold top and bottom case halves, 1979; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 24)
  - #2390: 2 cavity mold front cover, 1979; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 24)
  - #2392: 1 cavity mold (room for 2) loading door, 1979; made for Bur-Bak Machine Corp. (Box 24)
  - #2393: 4 cavity mold project 85 display lens, 1979; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 24)
  - #2394: 4 cavity mold project 85 batterhy cover, 1979; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 24)
  - #2400-2401: 4 cavity mold project 03 battery cover and large button set, 1979; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 24)
  - #2402: 2 cavity mold cover and base, 1979; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 24)
  - #2403: 6 cavity mold base housing and cover, 1979; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 24)
  - #2404: 2 cavity mold operations frame, 1979; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 24)
  - #2405: 2 cavity mold operations frame, 1980; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 24)
  - #2407: 4 cavity mold project 3 small button set, 1980; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 24)
  - #2412: 10 cavity mold 4031 slip dis parts, 1980; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 24)
  - #2421: 1 cavity mold basket adult/juvenile, 1980; made for Bur-Bak Machine Corp. (Box 24)
  - #2422: 1 cavity mold feed rod trunk, 1980; made for Bur-Bak Machine Corp. (Box 25)
  - #2424: 5 cavity mold quartz heater parts, 1980; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 25)
  - #2425: 1 cavity mold cover housing, 1980; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 25)
  - #2430: 2 cavity mold 4" square flower pot, 1980; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 25)
  - #2431: 2 cavity mold bezel and housing mech., 1980; made for ICL Inc. (Box 25)
  - #2432: 1 cavity mold display housing, 1980; made for ICL Inc. (Box 25)
  - #2434: 4 cavity mold halt lok parts, 1980; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 25)
  - #2435: 4 cavity mold drive gear item 4955 big cat, 1980; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 25)
  - #2437: 12 cavity mold 4146 and 4955 gears, 1980; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 25)
  - #2438: 8 cavity mold 4146 right-left lens, 1980; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 25)
  - #2440: 8 cavity mold project 53 scorekeeper, 1980; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 25)
  - #2441: 2 cavity mold 4146 front-rear head, 1980; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 25)
  - #2444: 18 cavity mold 4541 parts, 1980; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 25)
  - #2445: 2 cavity mold 4111 board support, 1980; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 26)
  - #2450: Unidentified, 1980; made for Instrumentation Laboratory Inc. (Box 26)
  - #2451: 4 cavity mold accessories lid, 1980; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 26)
  - #2459: 1 cavity mold top coger GL 2550, 1980; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 26)
  - #2460: 1 cavity mold top cover GL 1450, 1980; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 26)
  - #2461: 1 cavity mold bottom cover GL 2550, 1980; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 26)
  - #2463: 8 cavity mold sneak attack fire button proj. 44, 1980; made for Boyden Plastics (Box 26)
  - #2466: 4 cavity mold 11776 battery cover, 1980; made for Parker Brothers (Box 26)
  - #2467: 4 cavity mold reflex lens, 1980; made for Parker Brothers (Box 26)
  - #2468: 4 cavity mold stand off ring, 1980; made for Parker Brothers (Box 26)
  - #2469: 1 cavity mold 1-bulb bracket, 1980; made for Flowtron (Box 26)
  - #2470: 12 cavity mold (4 cavity screen type insulator, 8 cavity grid spacer insulator), 1980; made for Flowtron (Box 26)
  - #2473: 4 cavity mold 4149 tower and bottom housing, 1980; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 26)
  - #2474: 14 cavity mold 4149 parts mold, 1980; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 26)
  - #2472: 2 cavity mold, 1.5 liter canister lid, 1980; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 26)
  - #2475: 2 cavity mold 4149 rotating drum, 1980; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 26)
  - #2476: 8 cavity mold spinner hub, 1980; made for Parker Brothers (Box 26)
  - #2481: 8 cavity mold plus 2 extra insulators, 1980; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 26)
  - #2486: proposed design 12 cavity handle mold, 1980; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 26)
  - #2489: 4 cavity mold lipstick container cover, 1981; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 26)
  - #2490: 4 cavity mold lipstick container base, 1981; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 26)
  - #2493: 12 cavity mold Avon cake knife handle, 1981; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 27)
  - #2498: 1 cavity mold coner insert, 1981; made for Hebert Tool Co. (Box 27)
  - #2502: 4 cavity (room for 9) mold for dust cover, 1981; made for Nypro (Box 27)
  - #2511: 2 cavity mold challenge yahtzee tray, 1981; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 27)
  - #2512: record player, 1981; made for Dejay Inc. (Box 27)
  - #2515: 1 cavity mold keyboard bracket, 1981; made for F&M Tool & Die Co. (Box 27)
  - #2522-2523: 2 and cavity mold Ford alt. comp. parts, 1981; made for F&M Tool & Die Co. (Box 27)
  - #2524: 4 cavity mold 4664 memory card tray, 1981; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 27)
  - #2525: 6 cavity mold MI case and parts, 1981; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 27)
  - #2535: 4 cavity mold probe tray, 1981; made for Parker Brothers (Box 27)
  - #2536: 1 cavity mold pusher dog single lug, 1981; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 27)
  - #2537: Unidentified1293, 1981; made for Instrumentation Laboratory Inc. (Box 27)
  - #2540: 1 cavity mold pneumatics door, 1981; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 27)
  - #2541: 2 cavity mold 4209 quibble base and cover, 1981; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 27)
  - #2542: 3 cavity mold rom pak parts, 1981; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 27)
  - #2543: 1 cavity mold pc board frame, 1981; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 27)
  - #2544: 48 cavity mold stratego pawn, 1981; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 28)
  - #2546: 2 cavity mold buckle parts, 1981; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 28)
  - #2552: 40 cavity mold survive token, 1981; made for Parker Brothers (Box 28)
  - #2554: 2 cavity mold 4208 trap door parts, 1981; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 28)
  - #2558-2559: 2 cavity mold pre-mold 25 pin D sub, 1981; made for F&M Tool & Die Co. (Box 28)
  - #2560: 1 cavity mold 6" food tray, 1981; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 28)
  - #2561: 1 cavity mold 8" food tray, 1981; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 28)
  - #2563: 1 cavity mold GL series hood, 1981; made for Flowtron (Box 28)
  - #2567: 2 cavity mold carriage and cover plate, 1981; made for Orion Research Inc. (Box 28)
  - #2568: 1 cavity mold tray, 1981; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 28)
  - #2569: 1 cavity mold tray cover, 1981; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 28)
  - #2567[?]: 480 cavity mold item 4000 life peg, 1981; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 28)
  - #2573: 4 cavity mold battery cover (lost treasure), 1981; made for Parker Brothers (Box 28)
  - #2574: 8 cavity mold potting cup, 1981; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 28)
  - #2575: 1 cavity mold cannister bottom, 1981; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 28)
  - #2577: 1 cavity mold support panel, 1981; made for Parker Brothers (Box 28)
  - #2578: 2 cavity mold adaptor clip, 1981; made for Parker Brothers (Box 28)
  - #2580: 4 cavity mold 4243 posts and motor mounts, 1982; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 28)
  - #2581: 8 cavity mold nose cap, 1982; made for Parker Brothers (Box 28)
  - #2583: 2 cavity mold valve housing, 1982; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 28)
  - #2587: 28 cavity mold 4233 parts, 1982; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 29)
  - #2590: 2 cavity mold right and left side panel, 1982; made for Leominster Die Service (Box 29)
  - #2593: 24 cavity mold 4203 Donkey Kong parts, 1982; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 29)
  - #2594: 24 cavity mold 4206 Frogger parts, 1982; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 29)
  - #2596: 1 cavity unit mold for wire block, 1982; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 29)
  - #2597: 2 cavity reevoir handle, 1982; made for General Electric (Box 29)
  - #2598: 2 cavity charafe handle, 1982; made for General Electric (Box 29)
  - #2602: 1 cavity mold fitting forward bulk head, 1982; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 29)
  - #2616: 2 cavity mold scream cover and base, 1982; made for Hebert Tool Co. (Box 29)
  - #2617: 1 cavity mold 14311 hood, 1982; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 29)
  - #2618: 1 cavity mold bulb boot mounting plate, 1982; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 29)
  - #2620: 8 cavity mold double nursoy scoop, 1982; made for Hebert Tool Co. (Box 29)
  - #2621: 12 cavity mold double prom scoop, 1982; made for Hebert Tool Co. (Box 29)
  - #2624: single cavity mold top and bottom cover, 1982; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 29)
  - #2625: 8 cavity mold 4340 (4 cav guide, 4 cav cap), 1982; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 29)
  - #2626: 4 cavity mold type "m" cartridge cover, 1982; made for Parker Brothers (Box 29)
  - #2629: 8 cavity mold 4340 parts, 1982; made for Parker Brothers (Box 29)
  - #2631: 10 cavity mold 4340 knob parts, 1982; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 30)
  - #2633: 4 cavity mold potting cup and bobbin, 1982; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 30)
  - #2634: single cavity mold for basket base GL7580 and 14313, 1982; made for Flowtron (Box 30)
  - #2635: 2 cavity mold cover tray, 1982; made for Parker Brothers (Box 30)
  - #2638: 1 cavity (room for 2) mold dummy phase shifter, 1982; made for Lee Plastics Inc. (Box 30)
  - #2640: 1 cavity mold cover bulb retainer, 1982; made for Lee Plastics Inc. (Box 30)
  - #2641: 8 cavity dial mold, 1982; made for Parker Brothers (Box 30)
  - #2643: 16 cavity mold foot set, 1982; made for Parker Brothers (Box 30)
  - #2648: 1 cavity spool mold, 1982; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 30)
  - #2656: 2 cavity mold display window, 1983; made for Parker Brothers (Box 30)
  - #2659: 2 cavity mold digital rainbow 100 dress panel, 1983; made for Parker Brothers (Box 30)
  - #2663: 6 cavity mold single pole bat lever, 1983; made for Parker Brothers (Box 30)